{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Chapter7.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "posso avere la carta di vini?",
                "posso avere la carta dei vini?"
            ],
            "answer": "Posso avere la carta dei vini?",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1486146628.0689628,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"May I have the wine list?\"?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il cameriere",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1486146605.6098342,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the waiter\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prendo il pesce al griglia",
                "prendo il pesce all griglia",
                "Prendo il pesce all griglia"
            ],
            "answer": "Prendo il pesce all griglia.",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1486146723.3829293,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I'll have the grilled fish.\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il secondo"
            ],
            "answer": "il secondo (piatto)",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1486146611.2732494,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the main (course)\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "posso pagare con la carta di credito",
                "posso pagare con la carta di credito?"
            ],
            "answer": "Posso pagare con la carta di credito?",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1486146758.7825103,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Can I pay by credit card?\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tu ordini",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1486146483.4360585,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you order (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'antipasto",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1486146479.092293,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the appetizer\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il conto",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1486146669.0961695,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the check\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ha"
            ],
            "answer": "lei ha",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1486146761.861942,
            "question": "she (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il dolce",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1486146837.768487,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the dessert\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro hanno"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro hanno",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1486146841.5359883,
            "question": "y'all (formal) (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "primo (piatto)"
            ],
            "answer": "il primo (piatto)",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1486146792.297211,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the first (course)\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vorrei i ravioli al ragu'"
            ],
            "answer": "Vorrei i ravioli al ragu'.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146808.0210686,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I would like ravioli with meat sauce.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ha"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei ha",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1486146797.0651014,
            "question": "you (formal) (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ordina"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei ordina",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146820.356844,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you order (formal)\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prendi"
            ],
            "answer": "tu prendi",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146766.6299777,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you take, you'll have (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ordina"
            ],
            "answer": "lui/lei ordina",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146854.452123,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"he/she orders\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prendo"
            ],
            "answer": "io prendo",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1486146861.675748,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I take, I'll have\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the side dish",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146897.7948987,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il contorno\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sono"
            ],
            "answer": "loro sono",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1486146904.9629629,
            "question": "they (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "avete"
            ],
            "answer": "voi avete",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146866.3478773,
            "question": "y'all (informal) (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prende",
                "lei prende"
            ],
            "answer": "lui/lei prende",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1486146849.0645218,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"he takes/she takes, he'll have/she'll have\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la mancia",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1486146923.162737,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the tip\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "prende"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei prende",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1486146926.8628135,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you take, you'll have (formal)\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la cameriera",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146931.6702116,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the waitress\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il contorno",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146945.1262243,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the side dish\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "can I"
            ],
            "answer": "can I, may I",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1486147004.0929613,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"posso\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the check",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486146948.0136385,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il conto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la carta dei vini",
                "carta dei vini"
            ],
            "answer": "la lista dei vini, la carta dei vini",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486147001.6047027,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the wine list\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "prendere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486146953.2060027,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to take (or, to have, as in an order)\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I'll have the grilled fish"
            ],
            "answer": "I'll have the grilled fish.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1486146997.253084,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Prendo il pesce all griglia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sono"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro sono",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486146958.2495165,
            "question": "y'all (formal) (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sono"
            ],
            "answer": "io sono",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486147030.7246234,
            "question": "I (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho"
            ],
            "answer": "io ho",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147035.7886965,
            "question": "I (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "siete"
            ],
            "answer": "voi siete",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486147009.5688767,
            "question": "y'all (informal) (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "he/she takes"
            ],
            "answer": "he takes/she takes, he'll have/she'll have",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486147025.4086096,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lui/lei prende\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "e'"
            ],
            "answer": "lei e'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147019.0249844,
            "question": "she (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ordinare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147038.9001508,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to order\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to take"
            ],
            "answer": "to take (or, to have, as in an order)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147027.745205,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prendere\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to order",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147042.0207627,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ordinare\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "e'"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei e'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147058.50354,
            "question": "you (formal) (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the waiter",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147045.092651,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il cameriere\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I'll have the ravioli with meat sauce"
            ],
            "answer": "I would like ravioli with meat sauce.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147086.834485,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Vorrei i ravioli al ragu'.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the main course"
            ],
            "answer": "the main (course)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147048.8716586,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il secondo (piatto)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I take"
            ],
            "answer": "I take, I'll have",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147051.271955,
            "question": "Given the definition \"io prendo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "e'"
            ],
            "answer": "lui e'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147063.6235213,
            "question": "he (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sei"
            ],
            "answer": "tu sei",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147074.9316974,
            "question": "you (informal) (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the fresh fruit",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147089.7466524,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la frutta fresca\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Can I have the wine list",
                "Can I have the wine list?"
            ],
            "answer": "May I have the wine list?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147123.210468,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Posso avere la carta dei vini?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the first course"
            ],
            "answer": "the first (course)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147101.6548176,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il primo (piatto)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "siamo"
            ],
            "answer": "noi siamo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147108.3144445,
            "question": "we (Essere (to be)):",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la frutta fresca",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147094.5869052,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the fresh fruit\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you take (formal)"
            ],
            "answer": "you take, you'll have (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147115.066475,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei prende\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "he/she orders",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147105.4985647,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lui/lei ordina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the waitress",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147131.334138,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la cameriera\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "abbiamo"
            ],
            "answer": "noi abbiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147136.118289,
            "question": "we (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the tip",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147138.7181609,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la mancia\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the restaurant",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147157.8250625,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il ristorante\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "posso",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147142.8616216,
            "question": "Given the definition \"can I, may I\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the wine list",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147160.3770454,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la lista dei vini, la carta dei vini\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ordino"
            ],
            "answer": "io ordino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147145.4380102,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I order\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ha"
            ],
            "answer": "lui ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147179.7049325,
            "question": "he (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the appetizer",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1486147190.9328759,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'antipasto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hanno"
            ],
            "answer": "loro hanno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147163.6572995,
            "question": "they (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dessert"
            ],
            "answer": "the dessert",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147208.396526,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il dolce\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the menu",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147210.3651462,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il menu'\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you order"
            ],
            "answer": "you order (informal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147205.1086488,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tu ordini\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il ristorante",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147225.2085793,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the restaurant\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "I order",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147193.1726322,
            "question": "Given the definition \"io ordino\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you take"
            ],
            "answer": "you take, you'll have (informal)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147227.3367758,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tu prendi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Can I pay by credit card"
            ],
            "answer": "Can I pay by credit card?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147201.5085807,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Posso pagare con la carta di credito?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il menu"
            ],
            "answer": "il menu'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147212.5716693,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the menu\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hai"
            ],
            "answer": "tu hai",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1486147252.7072587,
            "question": "you (informal) (Avere (to have)):",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you order"
            ],
            "answer": "you order (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1486147241.500053,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei ordina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        }
    ]
}